themisbar.com 2010-12-21

# Themis Bar Review

### Effective

This Privacy Policy was last modified on February 2, 2009. 

### Information Practices

Themis Bar Review, LLC ("Themis") understands that security and privacy are important issues for visitors to the ThemisBar.com website (the "Site") and recognizes its obligations to keep your information secure and confidential. We maintain the standards set forth in this Privacy Policy to help protect information that personally identifies you. By using the Site, you agree to comply with and be bound by all terms, conditions, and notices contained or referenced in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, which we also urge you to read. If you do not agree to these terms, you are prohibited from using the Site. 

### Collection of Information

You may be asked to voluntarily provide your name, billing address, law school, telephone number, email address, credit card number or other personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") to make purchases or to have access to some features of the Site. By using the Site and providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to our use of such information as described in this Privacy Policy. You may always refuse to provide your Personal Information, but this may lead to our inability to provide you with certain products or services. 

Themis or its business partners may also collect information that is anonymous, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet (for example, "aol.com"); the Internet Protocol ("IP") address of the computer you are using (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider); the browser software you use and your operating system; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to this Site (collectively, "Anonymous Information"), through the use of cookies or by other means. We hope that, by using Anonymous Information, we can update the Site to make it more useful to you and other users. We reserve the right to maintain, update, disclose or otherwise use Anonymous Information, without limitation. 

### Use of Information

Themis uses your Personal Information for the following purposes: to process your orders and administer your account; to administer and improve the Site and related services; to notify you of our products, services, promotional events or special offers that may be of interest to you; to provide Internet security; and to meet legal requirements. We may work with our business partners who may perform certain functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, sending email messages related to your purchases or inquiries, managing data, processing credit card payments or providing customer service. These business partners have access to your Personal Information only to the extent necessary to perform these specific functions and may not use it for any other purpose. 

Other than for the specific purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information unless we obtain your prior consent or are legally required to do so. We may use third party advertising companies to place ads on the Site and to place our ads on other websites. These companies may use Anonymous Information about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements on the Site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If Themis is involved in the sale of a substantial portion of its business assets, Anonymous or Personal Information may be among the transferred assets. 

### Legal Disclosure

Themis may disclose your Personal Information or otherwise use such information if required or permitted to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process or any governmental request; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Themis or its business partners; (3) enforce the Terms of Use or any applicable agreements; or (4) protect the personal safety or interests of Themis employees, users of the Site or members of the public in urgent circumstances. Themis may also disclose your Personal Information to a third party that alleges that you have infringed their intellectual property rights, subject to reasonable verification of such claims. 

### Forums

Themis may provide forums to users of the Site. Any information that is disclosed in the forums is public information and users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose Personal Information. If you voluntarily disclose Personal Information in a public area of the Site, such as a forum, that information may be collected and used by a third party to send you unsolicited messages, advertisements or for other purposes. Themis does not control the actions of these third parties in forums and other public areas of the Site. If you disclose Personal Information in a public area, you do so at your own risk. Further, any communications within the Site and forums travel through Themis' servers and any such communications that you send or receive may be monitored by Themis. 

### Cookies 

When you visit the Site, Themis or a third party advertiser may store or recognize some information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file that can help us in many ways. A cookie is a bit of information that is stored on a visitor's hard drive that allows the Site to track how a visitor navigates through the Site and areas in which a visitor shows interest. Cookies track trends and behaviors, but do not personally identify individuals. Cookies allow us to tailor the Site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your Internet browser instructions to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, functionality of the Site may be limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of many of the Site's features. 

### Linking to Third Party Web Sites 

This Site contains links to websites operated by third parties. These links are provided to you for informational purposes only; once you connect with another website by choosing a link, you will no longer be on the Site. The posting of third party websites does not represent Themis' endorsement or support of the linked organization, its programs or services, or the content included on its website. Please review each linked website's privacy policy, and if you do not agree to be bound by the terms of the policy governing that website, terminate your visit to that website. We are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or content of websites operated by third parties. For more information about linking to third party websites, please review our Terms of Use. 

### Your Opportunity to Opt-out of Email Advertising

In the event you do not wish to receive promotional email from Themis, follow the opt-out instructions contained within the body of any email message you receive. 

### Security 

Themis has policies and procedures in place to protect the privacy and confidentiality of your Personal Information that it collects and maintains. We have industry standard security programs intended to keep Personal Information stored in our systems and server shielded from unauthorized access. We store all Personal Information in secure data centers located within the United States. These systems are configured with data encryption or other scrambling technologies and firewalls constructed to high industry standards. Any unauthorized use of the Site may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution. 

### No Guarantee 

Themis will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your Personal Information; nonetheless transmissions on the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Themis assumes no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your Personal Information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control. 

### Privacy of Children

Themis encourages parents and guardians to be aware of and participate in their children's online activities. We strictly adhere to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personal Information from any child under the age of 13 in any manner that violates this law. 

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our home page and by posting the date of the most recent revisions to the Privacy Policy on this page. We urge you to review the Privacy Policy from time to time, as your continued use of the Site indicates your agreement to the revised terms. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will become effective immediately upon being posted on the Site, unless otherwise indicated. 

### Contact Us 

If you have any concerns about privacy procedures at this Site or wish to access or modify your Personal Information collected at this Site, please email us at [info@ThemisBar.com](mailto:info@ThemisBar.com). Please make any communications as complete and descriptive as possible, and we will attempt to respond promptly to your concerns.
